André Luiz da Silva

Software Engineer

☐ jobs@andresilva.cc

% +55 47 99900-1415

⊕ andresilva.cc

github.com/andresilva-cc

A software engineer with professional experience in web systems and mobile applications. Led and participated in the project and development of applications for public and private companies in the most diverse segments, using programming languages and tools such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Vue.js, Drupal, PHP, Laravel, Node.js, and NativeScript.

Experience

Front-end Engineering Consultant @ Atlas Technologies

Mar 2022 - Present

Front-end Engineer @ Atlas Technologies

Nov 2021 - Mar 2022

Assignments in a squad:

- Front-end development for a platform with more than 20 million monthly visits
- Review of internal and external PRs
- Front-end responsible for the deployment process
- Tracking and organization of tasks in Jira using Scrum

CEO & Co-Founder @ Nuxstep

Jun 2018 - Oct 2021

- Planned and developed software projects
- Helped in the execution of IT infrastructure projects
- Helped in the daily activities of departments such as administrative, commercial, financial, support, among others
- Developed a plugin that integrates Spotify's SDK into NativeScript

Software Development Intern @ Gmaes Telecom

Mar 2017 - Dec 2018

- Helped in the development of a web inventory system for the City Hall of Francisco Beltrão using
 Vue.js and Laravel
- Planned, designed and developed the new website of the Federal Council of Engineering and Agronomy (CONFEA) using Drupal
- Developed an integration between the Nuvemshop e-commerce platform and SkyHub marketplace integrator
- Deployed applications on Linux and Windows servers

Education

UNIVALI - Universidade do Vale do Itajaí

2015 - 2019

Node.js

Bachelor of Computer Science

Technologies

HTML Express CSS SQL NativeScript Sass JavaScript Flutter **TypeScript** Adobe XD Figma Vue.js Drupal Java PHP Shell Script Linux Laravel

Windows Server